prudential plc is a british
multinational insurance company
headquartered in london england
it was founded in london in may 1848 to
provide loans
to professional and working people
here are some other information about
this particular insurance company
its type
is traded as
industry
founded
headquarters
area served
key people
products
revenue
its operating income
net income total assets
total equity number of employees and its
website
potential has 12 primary listings on the
london stock exchange and hong kong
stock exchange and is a constituent of
the ftse 100 index
it also has secondary listings on the
new york stock exchange and singapore
exchange